Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Let's get started, son.
Come on.
"In the name of God, the infinitely
Compassionate and Merciful." (Basmala).
Eternal Allah!
- Allah is Great!
- Allah is one!
My Osman, give it a break.
Everything has its time.
Everything has its time, son.
This is my wedding gift for my Aybars,
Bamsı Bey.
This weapon needs to be done before
the next night comes.
I kept my every word that I gave to him.
Look at them, hey!
Both my Osman and my Aybars grew up...
and they became blood brothers.
With my father Ertuğrul Ghazi, we follow
your friendship, my Bamsı Bey.
Thank my Allah.
Thank my Allah, I've seen these days.
Praise be my valiant!
Praise be! (Masha Allah)
So, my Osman, what do you think?
Will our Ertuğrul Ghazi return from Konya?
Will Sultan and Dahi Beys
accept his offer?
We realized our homeland's fire together
with...
my ancestor Alparslan in
Malazgirt, Bamsı Bey.
We were rookie, we are masters now.
We tolerated everything.
We fought fearlessly to...
call this land our homeland.
Now, it is time to turn these small
shrubs into a luscious tree.
Under the luscious tree, brave men
and magnificent women...
will pave the way for a new state.
All the enemies, all the traitors...
We will destroy them with this fire.
No matter what results come from Konya...
We won't let my father's flag fall.
May Allah be my witness...
my children and I will fight resolutely
to...
spread this blessed flag to
all the world.
Masha Allah (praise be).
Masha Allah my valiant.
Now that I heard these from you,
I will die in peace.
Our Ertuğrul Bey's objective is in
progress.
My father Süleyman Shah had this boil too.
Look at the difficulty this malady is
giving to me, Hatun...
while I have Ertuğrul Bey's trust in my
Shoulders.
Little things don't hurt the great.
You are Dündar Bey.
You will get over every difficulty
for sure.
Everybody looks, but my brother Ertuğrul
Bey sees.
We are harvesting what he seeded...
twenty-five years ago.
This agreement will bring
peace and welfare, Hatun.
Don't underestimate yourself, Dündar Bey.
You need to walk with friends, not strangers.
What would happen if you stepped back
like Gündoğdu and Sungurtekin?
Ertuğrul Bey gained power thanks to
your support.
Everyone has some power.
But only you have power and skills.
Also...
you talk about peace, but...
snakes, who fear from peace, are already
out there.
You need to be careful.
May my Allah be my witness...
I'll burn those snakes alive.
I will.
I gave my word to my brother Ertuğrul Bey.
I will carry this out.
Let's go.
Let's not keep Governor Yorgepolos wait.
I wish to be blessed by you before
taking off.
Oy, oy son.
Your father's prayers are always with you, son.
However, we can't trust them.
Be careful, son.
Okay?
Don't worry, father. I am the son of
retired Head Alp Bamsı.
The enemy who faces me knows that I am
the winner.
Thank you, son.
Thank you (Eyvallah)
However...
you should know that...
braveness cannot always deal with treason.
You need to be careful.
You need to foresee the enemy behind you.
Who can foresee the enemy, father?
Bey does, son.
Bey(Master) knows.
Look, this is my Oğuz Ancestor's advice.
Whatever happens to Oğuz happens whilst
he sleeps.
The valiant who doesn't sleep can foresee,
son.
Some people are walking asleep.
However, Bey, who is awake even if when
he sleeps...
can foresee the enemy, son.
I think you missed Ertuğrul Ghazi, father.
Oy, my Ertuğrul Bey.
No, son.
You miss who you can't see.
You have miss who you can't see.
Son...
I see Ertuğrul Bey in Osman.
His looks, his behaviors, his stand...
He carries them all.
You cannot see a valiant like him
every day.
Son, my wish is that you shall be
among the ones who are with him.
Look, son. This is not a will from father.
This is a will from your ancestor.
Stand with Osman...
just like I stood with Ertuğrul Bey.
Ayşe Hatun.
Shall we take our traditional
carpets to them also?
I knew you would want them too,
my Gündüz Bey(master)
- I prepared them last night.
- Thank you (Eyvallah) Hatun.
Thank you. (Eyvallah)
It is obvious that you are from here.
Let's go.
Hay Masha Allah (praise be!)
Masha Allah.
- Burçin.
- Aybras.
Do you have to go?
We have henna night tonight.
Stay in the tent.
You know,
mission is the priority for the Alps.
Also, I can't leave Osman Bey
alone, Burçin.
Pray for us so that we can go fast and
come back well.
In sha Allah (if Allah permits).
May Allah open your road, Aybars.
Just a little time left.
Tonight, these hands will
be applied henna of our wedding.
Aygul prepared henna for me.
It was so beautiful.
If only you could see yourself
in the view of my eyes.
You are so beautiful.
Go.
They are waiting for you.
My Burçin, you are entrusted to Allah.
You too, my Aybars.
You too.
Ey Kayı's Alps(men)
You are ready to fire.
Your body shows nobility, and your
heart shows the fire inside you.
- Masha Allah, Masha Allah! (praise be!)
- Thank you (Eyvallah) my Bey!
What are these, son?
These are the weapons we will
present to the governor, father.
Osman, you are the master of weapons here.
Check them, see if our friend Governor
Yorgepolos would like these.
We will give these as a gift.
And, we are going to attack...
his castle with these weapons.
Why wouldn't he like it, Dündar Bey?
Dündar Bey.
Other than Kayıs are strangers.
Just in case...
shall I come with you?
What do you say?
We need a hand in our tent, Bamsı Bey.
You stay here, finish the preparations,
and take care of the tent.
Okay(Eyvallah) Dündar Bey.
Let us depart.
Come on.
You are entrusted to Allah.
Go fast and come back well.
Tekfur Yorgopolos, both the peace and
trade agreements are like what we want.
However, the indemnity for caravan raids
cannot be accepted.
Don't worry, Kalanos.
- No power can make me sign it.
- I don't have any doubt.
We paved the way for this agreement with
Ertuğrul, but...
his brother Dündar wants to be the man
to finish it.
Of course he wants.
He wants to show his power to everyone.
With god's will,
we will be superior all the time
This is a talisman which is to protect
my husband.
As long as you are with me, nothing can
hurt me.
I am a very lucky man.
We should be careful anyways.
The stars on the sky last night
annoyed me.
You may consider this a superstition, but
they annoyed me.
Don't worry about me, Sofya.
Commander Kalanos, the greatest warrior of
Bithynia...
is to protect me.
Kayıs are coming, sir.
Respected Governor!
Welcome (in distance)
- Welcome, Dündar Bey.
- Thank you Governor Yorgopolos.
Princess Sofia.
Welcome, Kayı's women.
You honored our castle.
We are honored too, princess.
I wish Ertuğrul Bey had been with us
on this beautiful day.
We owe this happiness to him.
The show is starting.
Ertuğrul!
If what you want is me, Governor,
here I am!
Neither I nor you fear from each other...
until this day.
Let's finish this!
Enough!
This war should end.
I want to build trust between us.
Shall my people have a full belly and
a happy heart.
Long live!
We decided to fight till the last
drop of our blood.
Now we decided to make peace.
Long live!
Then, with my brother Dündar...
we shall make peace with you.
I'll go to Konya.
When I come back, we will celebrate
this agreement.
Governor Yorgopolos, you are an honorable
man.
You are wise as well as a good soldier.
As to Ertuğrul Bey...
All the Bithynia knows how brave he is.
He feeds the poors.
He clothes the naked.
He saves the debtor.
He doesn't distinguish müslims and
non-müslims.
Ertuğrul Ghazi and his sons' friendship
is eternal...
and their hostility is the enemy's end.
Protect the Governor.
Alps (men) get in the position!
Alps(men), get in the position.
This is treason!
This is your castle, and those are your
soldiers.
How could you let this treason happen?
Whose dog are you?
Who are you?
Speak up!
Stop him!
End him!
Osman.
This castle is in sedition also, brothers.
- Is everyone okay?
- Thanks to you, Osman.
Thank Allah.
If we don't figure out who is behind this,
sleep is haram (forbidden) for us.
They will pay for this sooner or later.
In this hard to live land, in Bithynia,
do you know how did I survive...
and stay strong, Nizamettin Efendi? (Mr.)
By smelling everything.
Both good and evil have a smell.
No matter what you are, evil or good...
you have to have a smell.
Now, tell me.
What is the situation?
Kayıs have gone to the castle, Alişer Bey.
They will make an agreement with
the Governor.
Do you think Governor will accept it?
They are going with gifts.
Greeks are preparing a celebration.
I am the letter, I am the pen, I am
the agreement in this land.
Without me, that agreement is worthless.
This will break the Yenipazar (the bazaar)
If they make an agreement, Söğütpazarı
(another bazaar) will rise in value.
Obviously, this is going to be critical.
But they miss something.
The side that I am in always win.
Zöhre Hatun.
This incident has hurt me.
I am so sorry.
You can't get away with it by saying
sorry, princess.
It was really devastating.
It was an inappropriate situation for
the great Kuluca Castle.
Your castle is very elegant,
but obviously, its doors are weak.
This disaster wouldn't have happened...
if someone from inside hadn't helped.
Yorgopolos will find the traitors
as fast as possible.
Thanks to your braveness and militancy...
my beloved husband is still alive.
He always praised Kayıs.
Everyone would do the same.
Peace and friendship needs this.
This is why we are here, right?
There are obstacles in peace and
friendship.
The incident showed this to us.
Apart from the Governor,
this attack was against my man also.
As you said, I hope traitors will be found
as fast as possible, in sha Allah.
Otherwise, neither Dündar Bey nor I will
drop this subject for sure (Evelallah)!
- Excuse my apologize, Dündar Bey.
- Why would I?
Me, Governor Yorgopolos...
You need to find whoever did this...
for me to accept your apology.
Be sure that I'll find whoever did this.
It is obvious that we annoyed someone
by signing this agreement, Dündar Bey.
We almost died.
Why would we trust you that you
keep your word?
Furthermore, what about the conditions
that you have been postponing?
If it will make you trust me again...
- I am ready to accept them Dündar Bey.
- Governor Yorgopolos.
Are you sure?
Is making such an
important decision right?
This is right, Kalonoz.
Let's finish this today.
So that Kayıs don't suspect
our friendship.
What do you say, Gündüz Bey (master)?
I say we finish this here today,
my Dündar Bey.
When Ertuğrul Bey returns, we will
celebrate it in our tent.
Let's finish this then.
Let's sit.
What about the indemnity of trade
caravans?
These are so heavy conditions.
This is valid for both sides, Commander
Kalanos.
The one in whose lands crime happens...
will pay it.
After caravan raids, bandits have escaped.
The indemnity would effect both of us.
This is unaccaptable, Gündüz Bey.
Of course, it is acceptable,
Commander Kalanos.
Osman.
How, Osman Bey?
Bandits are reckless because they got
away with it.
Every word coming out of your mouth is
precious for me.
Continue your speech.
If you authorize me to cross Hudut
and catch them...
bandits will realize they cannot escape.
So, there will be no indemnity issue.
Do you trust in yourself that much,
Osman Bey?
He showed us his skillfulness today.
What do you say, Dündar Bey?
Your nephew Osman is right.
My nephew thought it well.
However, this way is both
hard and dangerous.
Not everyone manage chasing bandits.
If we give this mission to you, can you
manage it Osman Bey?
This cannot be acceptable, this disregards
our borders, Governor Yorgopolos.
If you give this mission to me and my
Alps...
and a Commander that you assign...
Kalanos would be relax too.
Now that Dündar Bey also approves, I give
you the permission for my borders.
I will arrange a Commander soon.
You can think this as a mark of your
braveness.
Thank you, Governor Yorgopolos.
To the bandits who crossed the border...
- Forgive, madam.
- Forgive madam.
Forgive us madam.
You couldn't even kill a old Governor.
You ruined my plan which I worked on
so much...
with your clumsiness.
Osman could have known you Migala.
Then, we couldn't explain anything.
Now, take your best man.
He must be killed in the first place.
Don't underestimate Osman.
He's not a random people.
He must definitely pay this.
Osman.
Osman, what do you think you're doing?
What, brother?
Osman, weapons are held by soldiers,
words are said by elders.
Why do you step in when
there's your uncle?
The true word is said in point.
La Hawla! Both you're looking for trouble
and you don't know your place?
And you're still talking!
No need to belabor.
Enjoy your meal.
Bora, stay here.
Aybars, come with me.
You'll look wonderful in your
henna night, Burçin.
-My Aybars will like me a lot.
-He'll like you no matter what.
One day, we'll hold a wedding for
you and Osman, Aygül.
-You think so?
-Of course.
When this time comes, I'll carry flour with
griddle and water with sieve for you.
Inshaallah, Allah grants us a happiness
like yours.
Insha'allah.
They'll ruin everything!
The only thing they care about is gold!
My uncle and my brother don't get it.
They don't see the sedition
in front of them.
Who dares that, Osman Bey?
It doesn't matter who dares, Aybars.
Fortune of Kayıs is kneaded in
the chela of scorpion.
We've always been under threat.
And we're on alert.
A great war will break out in this lands.
I feel it in my bones.
Never forget...
This war will be won by warriors
like eagle and hawk...
not by the ones who are
on alert like a pigeon.
A state will rise from our dreams.
A state...
You heard Dündar Beys.
You are talking about a state in the
middle of the turmoil, Osman Bey.
We won't sleep anymore, Aybars.
Things started to happen.
It's time to hunt.
Who are they, Osman Bey?
Evil isn't only in the castle, my Aybars.
Evil isn't only in the castle.
Ya Allah!
It's a trap, Aybars!
You take the left, I'll take the
right. Eternal Allah!
Allah is righteous!
Aybars!
Oh my Allah! Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Dropping blood stain on henna dress
brings bad luck, they say.
It's because of excitement, my Burçin.
You should interpret favourably.
Think good, then it'll be good. Today
is your henna day.
Aygül, they're not still back.
Why are you worrying about them?
First, we'll fit you nicely.
Then when he sees you, he'll be shocked.
My Allah, protect my Aybars.
Catch that Turk!
Come here, you smartasses.
Run this way!
www.kurulusosman.online
If I oppose Osman's offer in
front of Tekfur...
he'll think that we have hostility
between me and Osman.
Osman does whatever he wants!
If Osman storms around, you should rage.
Or his idle moves will bring
our tent harm.
Can I come in, uncle?
Come, Gündüz.
Uncle...
No news from Osman and Aybars.
They're not back.
Don't think of troubling things, Gündüz.
Uncle...
I don't feel comfortable.
Does Bamsı Bey know, Gündüz?
No, uncle.
Tell Alps to hit the road quickly.
Tell them to go and don't return
without finding them.
Your command, uncle.
He may need help.
We don't have much time.
He's alive.
We have to get him.
We have to raise him from the dunghill.
Pull...
Come on, boy. Pull!
Come on!
Come on, boy!
Come on! Come on, boy!
We lost so much time.
He's pulling around.
Help me. We have
to carry him.
We have to go
now. Come on.
Aybars!
Aybars...
Mashaallah! Come here, come.
Come.
Come here. Come...
I don't want to hurt you. I don't
want to hurt you at all.
But I wish to sacrifice you for Allah...
and offer you to Alps in my
Aybars' wedding.
Mashaallah!
Im grateful to you.
What would we do if...
Allah hadn't given you to us?
But would it be easy cutting my own son...
with our own knife...
to sacrifice him to Allah?
Would it be?
It wouldn't be. It wouldn't.
Do you know that story? Will you listen
to me if I tell you?
Listen to me, then.
Aybars!
Brother...
My brother...
My dear brother...
Thank Allah, before my death...
I saw you safe and sound.
People's fate save them from
their death, brother. Hang on!
Hang on! I'll carry you. Come on!
Hang on, brother.
Hang on, my Aybars.
Prophet Abraham's only wish...
was to have children.
He wanted from Allah and he said...
"If you give me a child, I'll
sacrifice him for you."
And Allah gave him a child
from our Mother Hacer.
Prophet Abraham named his child "İsmail."
İsmail grew up.
He was 7.
You look beautiful.
Great!
Smile a little bit.
A bride shouldn't sulk before her henna.
I'll complain about you when Aybars comes.
I'll tell him that my dear sister sulked
me when you're away.
I'm sorry, my Aygül. I upset you.
No, you don't.
Then Prophet Abraham saw a dream.
In his dream, he was said about
him sacrificing his child.
And Abraham went nearby İsmail...
and told him about his dream.
İsmail looked at his father's eyes...
He said "father"...
"Do what's necessary!"
İbrahim's heart was broken...
but the order was...
a holy order.
And he... he...
took İsmail and...
laid him down to his forehead.
He was about to stab him....
May it be hayır. (something good.)
I hope there's nothin wrong.
Is he Osman?
We're here.
Inform the healer quickly.
Come on!
Summon the healer!
Hang on, my Aybars!
Aybars...
Aybars!
Brother, we're here.
Give me...
your blessings.
"I bear witness that there is no god but Allah...
And I bear witness that Muhammad...
is the messenger of Allah." (Kalima Shahadah)
Aybars!
Aybars! Aybars!
Osman Bey!
You coluldn't save your brother!
How could you let him die? How!
Enough.
-How could you let him die?
-Enough.
Enough!
www.kurulusosman.online
Osman...
Tell me what happened.
We fell into a trap.
We fought with my brother, Bamsı Bey.
But I broke my words.
I couldn't save Aybars.
Forgive me.
A person who insists on going it...
is headed for trouble.
We couldn't teach you that, Osman.
My son Aybars...
died with his...
blood brother...
for our land.
I have no doubt that...
his blood brother did his best for him.
My Osman...
don't worry, my Osman.
Don't ever...
cry.
Keep your head up! Keep your head up...
You didn't do anything that
you were ashamed of.
Burçin.
My daughter...
My Aybars, your fiance...
couldn't come together with
his worldly lover but...
but he came together
with his eternal lover.
My girl... Burçin...
You'll be reuniting...
...on the other side.
Osman, excuse me.
I am...
..Bamsı Beyrek.
Kayı Tent's...
...Head Alp (Men).
Everyone saw...
...just now..
We had pitched the wedding tent..
But...
Aybars has...
..returned to dust.
He has gone to Prophet Muhammad...
...to drink shahada sherbet from his
hands.
While I was waiting for my
son's wedding...
...in my fate, there was seeing a martyr's
wedding.
I don't want sorrowful poets to weep.
I don't want anyone to cry!
I don't want women to rip their hairs,
men to rip their chests.
Now...
...it's the time of great feast.
Now it's the time of wedding.
Now it's the time of a magnificent day.
Thanks to Allah almighty...
I am now the father of a martyr.
I'm the father of a martyr.
Bamsı is a martyr's father!
A martyr's father, Bamsı is.
A martyr's father..
We have a wedding, brothers!
My child has come together with
his creator.
We have a wedding, brothers!
My child has come together with
his creator.
Come together with his
creator, my child has.
We have a wedding, brothers!
My child has come together with
his creator.
We have a wedding, brothers!
My child has come together with
his creator.
Madam.
Tell me Osman has died, Mekala.
He has escaped the swamp he was in, Madam.
I don't know how.
God damn it!
I hope this incompetence of yours...
...doesn't cause any more trouble.
Now get out of my face!
But his closest Alp (Men)...
Bamsı's son Aybars...
...now in Kayı Tent, everyone's crying
around his dead body, Madam.
We killed him.
I hope Osman got the message.
And does not poke about anymore.
I was waiting for you for days.
Thank god you finally came.
It was quite difficult.
But being chosen for such a holy duty,
has rested us.
How are our sire?
Is he healthy?
He's doing fine.
He's wondering about the
castle's situation.
As you know, Kuluca Hisar is of
more importance to him.
May God protect him.
We've heard that things were complicated.
Your assumption was correct.
There was an assassination attempt on
Tekfur Yorgopolos.
I've never seen her mistaken.
The close relations with The Turks he has
established made him a target.
This damned darkness we're after is
about the surround the whole castle.
They're also responsible for the
devil's breath in this castle's walls.
We don't have much time.
We have to fulfill our majesty's order and
find the treasure.
If we can't succeed, everything
goes down the drain.
They sent the code, right?
I'm satisfied. You never disappointed us
with the duties, you have taken.
It might be written with some secrets
from the bible.
It probably represents various codes.
If we can find clue's about the secrets,
I can solve the numbers.
Direction and place is probably hidden
with the numbers.
You've solved similar secrets written
with ancient alphabets.
Then we can get over this and...
We can confront your majesty with the
happiness of fulfilling a duty.
I prayed for you in the church,
Yorgopolos.
With God's help and, Kalanos' skills...
I'm sure we'll catch who's responsible.
But, are you sure that the traitors are
from the castle?
We were betrayed, Sofia.
And this betrayal was not from outside of
the castle, but from within.
Yorgopolos, if you're right,
this is terrifying.
Don't go back empty-handed, Kolonos.
Find a clue for me.
Or they will be trying again soon.
Yes sir.
My dear husband.
I watch the sky every night.
I read the marks the stars and
planets left for us.
I'm sure of one thing..
As long as you're alive..
..no one will destroy the order
you've established.
You're making a mistake, Osman. You're
making a mistake, know that.
You left the castle without
anyone's knowledge.
What happened, huh?
Aybars died.
He died because of you.
Don't you understand already?
What are you bragging about?
You stamped on me next to Tekfur.
I didn't say anything.
But... How could I stay silent to
this, Osman?
They're pushing Osman too much, mother.
Could he wanted it to be that way?
What's going to happen?
If your father Ertuğrul Bey was here,
what would he do?
Yes, tell your uncle.
This issue from now on is my issue uncle.
I will get Aybars' revenge.
I have to get my brother's revenge.
And about my father...
If Süleyman Şah's son Ertuğrul
Gazi was here..
He wouldn't blame me with my
brothers death...
...he'd run after the killers with us,
and turn Bitinia into hell for them.
Now, will you drag your Alps (Men) after
a revenge?
How many more families will your ruin
after Aybars', Osman?
One more mistake, if you make one
more mistake..
Your punishment will be very big, Osman.
Know that.
I accept my punishment, whatever it is.
I'd rather not pull myself together
ever again...
...than bow down to your every threat.
Osman, Osman I'm talking to you, Osman!
Get him somewhere silent, talk
manners into him.
So he doesn't cause any more trouble.
Mother...
Talk to my father, mother.
I don't want them to push Osman this much.
I know Osman.
He won't stop until he gets his
revenge.
My girl, you heard it yourself.
He won't listen to his Aga (Master), or
his uncle.
May Allah protect us.
[Call to Funeral prayer Salat al-Janazah]
"Blessing and peace be upon you"
"Be upon you our master"
"O Prophet of Allah!"
"Allah"
"Allah! Allah!"
"O Prophet of Allah!"
"Blessing and peace be upon you"
"Be upon you our master"
Hafsa...
Since you were gone from here...
...it has been 3655 days. (10 years)
That day, my Hafsa...
...we both died.
But..
..they only buried you.
Hafsa..
..then my son.
My cheerful flower.
I also lost him to the plague.
My little one melted away before my eyes.
The fate of these lands, is this.
In feasts, goats...
In wars...
...valiants are sacrificed.
Our Aybars has become a martyr.
So we could call...
...these lands our homeland.
It's time for revenge, brothers!
I swear on our fire-breathing horses!
I swear!
I swear on those who make
pain sweet!
I swear!
My brother...
If I don't get my brother Aybars'
revenge...
...may I be cut like an unripe crop with
my own dark steel.
...May my name be removed from the
monuments.
I swear!
The rumour spread from the Kulucahisar
Castle.
That's also where we'll look for those
who spilled Aybars' blood.
To learn who they get orders from...
...to learn what they're after, we'll get
inside the castle at night.
Who will you go to in the castle, my Bey?
Is there someone you trust?
Other than one person, there's
no one we'll trust.
And that's Tekfur.
Because he was the killers target.
Why will you get inside secretly, my Bey?
I must talk with Tekfur in private.
No one shall know.
Even the ones closest to him could
be his enemy.
What's your order?
Now listen to me carefully, brothers.
Praise him, son and the moon. Praise him,
all the shining stars.
You made him wear the shallow
waters like a dress.
And the waters were on top of mountains.
What are the meanings of these?
In the first part, it says that he hangs
the world on nothingness.
The Sun and the moon.
All the shining stars.
The sky...
We'll look for a sky in the castle.
He spreads the north on emptiness.
Is there a secret room to the
north of the castle?
Sofia's room.
I have seen the seven planets made of
alchemy metals there.
The place stars and planets reflect...
...in the magic room.
The holy entrustments are here.
Now we're very close to our secret.
Sofia...
Sofia what's the matter with you?
Talk to me.
I beg you talk to me! I'd do
everything for you.
I'm in great pain, Kalonoz.
And I can't stand this pain anymore.
This longing for you, hurts my insides.
I want to be with you already, Kalonoz.
I also want that a lot.
But Tekfur...
Tekfur Yorgopolos.
How could we do that to him?
God.. If God didn't want us
to be together...
... would he give this love to us?
Kalonoz...
You're my greatest test in this world.
Every day...
...every night, I'm in pain because
of your longing.
I die every time I see you with Tekfur.
But what are we going to do, Sofia?
What can we do?
Allow me, Kalonoz..
I'll consult the stars tonight, and
tomorrow night...
...I'll inform you.
I'll wait for it like no other
news I've waited for.
Allah almighty...
...let me revenge my brother Aybars,
and our martyr's like him.
Don't you worry. Don't even shed a tear.
Keep your head upright. Keep your
head upright.
Bamsı...
...has become a martyr's father.
A martyr's father, Bamsı has become.
Why are you so dreamy?
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
I daydreamed.
Come on already, smile.
Look, we're really close
You're right.
We've come very close.
We'll have completed our duty tomorrow.
Are you upset because of this?
Come on, smile some.
Or are you...
...thinking about him?
About who?
The Turk you saved.
I wonder who he was.
What was he looking for there?
I don't know who he is. But it's certain
that he's in your mind.
One shouldn't tell you anything.
We need to rest. We have a lot to
do tomorrow.
Come on.
Whites...
If...
...there a whites in my hairs..
..they fell from the wings of the angels
who carry my Aybars.
They fell from their wings.
Bamsı Bey...
A martyr's smell, is heavens smell.
Now it's time to bury our brother, to
scatter his scent to the Kayı Tent.
Come on, come on then valiants.
"We take refuge from the accursed Satan"
(Basmala)
"In the name of God, the infinitely
Compassionate and Merciful." (Basmala).
[Quran Yā sīn:36]
"Ya-Sin. By the Qur´an, full of Wisdom."
"Indeed you, [O Muhammad],
are from among the messengers,"
"On a straight path."
"[This is] a Revelation sent down by (Him),
the Exalted in Might, Most Merciful.:
-Allah is great!
"That you may warn a people
whose forefathers were not ...
...warned, so they are unaware.
(of the Signs of Allah)."
"Already the word has come into effect upon most of them, so they do not believe."
"We placed shackles around their necks, up to their chins, ...
...so they are stiff-necked."
Peace be upon you.
Are your goods fresh?
They're fresh my Bey, here.
Giddy up!
What do you want from me?
Who are you?
Do you know who I am? I'm a castle
employee.
You can't do anything to me.
Let go! Let go! Let me go!
I have lots of coins. I'll give you
all you want. Let go!
Don't worry, we'll give you the coins.
[Quran Al-Fatiha  (The opening) 1:7]
Read and pray for him.
"In the name of God, the infinitely
Compassionate and Merciful."
"Praise be to Allah,
Lord of all the worlds."
"The Compassionate, the Merciful.
Ruler on the Day of Reckoning."
You alone do we worship, and
You alone do we ask for help."
"Guide us on the straight path,"
"The path of those who
have received your grace"
"not the path of those who have brought
down wrath, nor of those who wander astray."
"Ameen"
We've lost my Aybars.
And now we...
...have buried him.
But...
..we...
...don't place a valiant's sword...
...until he's avenged!
Osman...
My Osman...
Son..
From now on, this sword is yours.
My friend, until we avenge Aybars..
...carry this with you.
Don't you worry, my Bamsı Bey.
The only place Aybars' killers will run
to, is their deaths!
I swear on my...
...friend, my blood brother Aybars'
dark sword...
...this sword, will be the end of
those who killed him.
Alps(Men)!
Don't you forget.
Each of you, are Azans!
May you not cease!
Each one of you, are flags!
May you not go down!
Each one of you...
...like my child Aybars..
..valiants!
May you give your lives!
But, may you not die!
But, may you not die valiants!
www.kurulusosman.online
-Efendi Yanis.
-I know everything, Sofia.
If it weren't for your guard Mekala,
you could have caught...
one of the assassins and make him
talk in our favor.
Tell me about Ertuğrul's son Osman, Sofia.
His father had his knife at our hearts.
But his son...
...Osman..
His eyes look like a predator's.
He has stabbed us with his unlucky
knife already.
I'm afraid he doesn't look like he'll let
us go without carving our insides.
Tonight, I want Tekfur's corpse...
...and Kalonoz' soul.
Now about Osman...
His fate won't be any different
from his friend's.
As you ordered, my Bey. This cart will
go up to the castle's heart.
I'll be alone when we get inside
the castle.
You be ready at the door.
If anything goes wrong, we'll have
to fight our way out.
Bismillah.
-May Allah help us all.
-Amen.
With Osman, his Alps (Men) also went
with him.
Oran, Erkut, Boğaç.
He made them like him.
He'll drag him like a flood.
What is this madman's problem, huh?
What is it?
Revenge.
Only if my father knew this.
What revenge will he get as an apprentice?
Looks like he sees himself responsible
for what happened to Aybars.
Osman is right only in this matter.
If he thinks like this, he's right.
For what happened to Aybars, he's
responsible.
But, what is going after revenge,
seeking blood alone?
This Tent, why are we here, Gündüz?
This is the border. Here, we eat sheep
with the wolf...
...then, cry with the shepherd.
Uncle..
Let him come back if Allah permits...
...then I'll give him such a lesson...
...don't you worry.
This is not a lesson matter, my nephew.
The chain that'll stop him, is in
my brother's hands.
He'll only listen to him.
Living with the fear of what will be
his next move...
...has tired me.
Only if my brother could come back
from Konya...
...then I could rest a little.
Stop!
Where is Aleksis? Who are you?
I'm Aleksis' cousin. He needs to rest for
a few days.
Okay, go through.
Hey, driver!
What do you have in the car?
- I brought wine for the castle kitchen.
- Isn't it also our right do drink from...
..these beautiful wines?
Of course it is.
It's good. Now go.
Your power, brings the
moon down from the sky.
To your magic, the stars above fall down.
Come in.
The time has come, Helen.
Let lovers come together now.
Sofia, what if we don't succeed?
Pessimism doesn't suit the souls
devoted to our holy father, Helen.
Go, open hope's door.
Be careful!
Bring that barrel too.
We took that much trouble,
can't leave without tasting it.
This is where we're at. The cellar.
I'll go from here, and enter Tekfur's
room from the balcony here.
Now go to the Alps (Men). Tell them
to watch everywhere. Streets, entrances...
Okay, my Bey.
What about him, my Bey?
Don't worry, Tekfur Yorgopolos.
It's me, Osman.
Osman Bey.
What are you doing here like this?
We're both after the same thing,
Yorgopolos.
The arrows shot at you, didn't
hit their targets. But...
...after they got out of the castle, they
reached my brother Aybars.
To Bamsı Bey's son Aybars?
They killed him.
They wanted to kill me because I saved
your life in the Castle
But my brother paid for this.
We are deceived, Osman.
Don't seek them outside, Yorgopolos.
Obviously, you have been betrayed.
I don't trust even your best men.
How can we reveal those traitors?
Who do you trust the most in the castle?
My wife Sofia, my Commander Kalanos,
and his assistant Andreas.
Will we consult them?
No. We will start with them.
They do not betray me.
Treason comes from the nearest.
Let it be.
We'll see if they are innocent.
What I want from you is that...
you let my three most trusted Alp (men)
in your Castle.
Let me, so we can find the traitor.
Then, we will sink into the treason like
this arrow.
From now on, we are destiny brothers,
Yorgopolos.
Deal, Osman Bey.
Osman stop.
The square must be crowded.
It is not right for you to get out
from the balcony.
Osman, hide here.
Guard, what was that noise?
Check it.
You, bring me wine.
Osman, come.
God help us all, Osman.
Osman?
What is Osman doing in
the governor's room?
Come!
Respected Tekfur.
- I need to tell you something.
- What is it?
But, I have to ask you to
spare my life before that, sir.
If you want me to spare your life,
then you brought me the bad news.
What is it?
- Are you going to spare my life, sir?
- Just talk!
Sir, I saw a terrible thing.
Your wife...
... Princess Sofia is cheating on you!
Are you sure?
I saw it with my own eyes, sir.
How could you do this to me?
How could you do this to me, Sofia?
-Kalonoz!
- Sofia, my love!
- What did the stars say?
- They said we will have each other at last.
I will never leave you.
I am so happy to be
able to touch you.
Sofia.
Kalanos!
- Governor Yorgopolos, listen to me.
- God damn you two!
I loved him, I didn't stop myself, it is
all my fault Yorgopolos, please leave him.
Kill me.
Damn the day I loved you, Sofia.
Die!
He's dead, my love.
My love, he's dead!
- We are free at last.
- Not yet.
They can't find this body here.
After we throw him away, let us
go to our rooms and play our game.
Come on.
- Hurry, Boray Alp, we're leaving.
- Have you seen the governor, my Bey?
He's dead, my Bey.
Let's go, if they find out we
are here, they will blame us!
We won't leave until we
find out what is going on.
Wait for my word.
I know you.
You were the one who saved
my life in the swamp.
I thought you were an angel.
Leave here.
Speak first, who are you?
You asked for it, then come and find out.
Then let's find out who is
hiding behind this angelic face.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com